İletişim Bilgileri

taylanhersek@rogstudios.com

www.linkedin.com/in/taylanhersek (LinkedIn) www.rogstudios.com/ (Company) jackwalkerethereal.com/ (Company)

www.artstation.com/taylanhersek (Portfolio)

En Önemli Yetenekler

Agile Project Management Business Development Virtual Reality (VR)

Languages

German (Elementary)
Turkish (Native or Bilingual)
English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Blender Character Creator v2.0 for Video Games Design
Artırılmış Gerçeklik - 1

Build A Multiplayer Augmented Reality (AR) Game With Unity AgilePM® Foundation

Artırılmış Gerçeklik - 2

Taylan Hersek

AR/VR Project Manager & Co-Founder at ROG Studios istanbul

Özet

While I was studying Project Management in the UK, I did my research about VR and AR. My dissertation's title was "The Applications of Virtual/Augmented Reality in Construction Project Management". After I realized that I love working with the 'reality technologies' I decided to put myself into the VR industry and the first step was to go into the gaming sector.

Now, we're working on a Sci-Fi/RPG game for SteamVR, that's coming out this summer. Our game has unique movement mechanics and realistic graphics. We aim to take VR to the next level with this advanced game. It's a difficult game for beginners to get used to but it's really fun for experienced VR users. I'm the project manager of ROG Studios and we are not here to only make games.

We also aim to create B2B VR experiences and simulations for education, marketing and training purposes. During my research for my dissertation, I have seen a lot of different use cases for VR and AR, naturally I want to apply these technologies to various industries, with ROG Studios. I hope that Turkish people will realize the power of VR and AR and Turkish companies and schools will invest in these technologies, just like the rest of the world.

Our second step in reality technologies is, education. We aim to use augmented and virtual reality to educate young students, especially in these Covid-19 times. Students who are between 8-16 years old, do not enjoy online classes, because frankly, they're boring for kids (and for most of adults). However, when they start learning with AR using their phones, they will love learning and they won't forget what they learn, because they will learn by doing, not watching. Also, after they come back to school, when the virus situation eases off, we want schools to buy and use VR headsets in classes to teach them abstract concepts, because young children can't simply visualize 3D abstract things, but if they learn in VR, by interacting with 3D objects,

then they won't forget what they learn. Because, in order to learn a 3D concept, you should learn it in a 3D environment, and I propose learning with VR and AR. Imagine teaching kids about animal cells... Would you rather teach this 3D subject using a 2D platform, such as a computer screen or a book, or would you rather "be inside the cell". So, our next objective is to educate young students with AR and VR. Of course, we want to expand this technology to high schools and universities too...

Deneyim

ROG Studios AR/VR Producer & Co-Founder Ekim 2019 - Present (11 ay) Kartal

Project Manager of a Sci-fi/RPG Virtual Reality game for SteamVR Release date: Summer 2020

Also working on educational AR/VR projects

Istanbul Bilgi University Technology Lab Coordinator Kasım 2019 - Ocak 2020 (3 ay) Istanbul, Turkey

Solent University
Masters Student
Eylül 2018 - Eylül 2019 (1 yıl 1 ay)
Southampton, United Kingdom

PRINCE2 & AgilePM

Cambro Manufacturing Industrial Engineering Intern Temmuz 2017 - Ağustos 2017 (2 ay) Istanbul, Turkey

IZOCAM TİCARET VE SANAYİ A.Ş Marketing Intern Haziran 2017 - Temmuz 2017 (2 ay) Maltepe

Tekfen Engineering
Project Support
Temmuz 2016 - Ağustos 2016 (2 ay)
Business Development and Planning Department

Kahve Dünyası Production planning intern Temmuz 2016 - Ağustos 2016 (2 ay)

Istanbul, Turkey

Eğitim

Solent University

Master of Science - MS, Project Management · (2018 - 2019)

Ozyeğin Üniversitesi

Bachelor of Science - BS, Industrial Engineering · (2014 - 2018)

Üsküdar Amerikan Lisesi / Üsküdar American Academy (2009 - 2014)

Çamlıca Bilfen Koleji

· (2006 - 2009)